LYNETTE ANNE CARGO

Dallas, TX | lynettecargo@gmail.com | (469) 441 - 7105 | linkedin.com/in/lynette-anne-cargo

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Versatile, organized Software Engineer with outstanding customer service experience. A smart and creative fast learner with extensive experience working in fast paced environments demanding strong organizational, technical, and interpersonal skills.

A confident and poised professional with the ability to assess situations and create solutions while exercising a calm demeanor in stressful situations. A team player who is comfortable working with others at all levels as well as individually.

EDUCATION

Per Scholas, Dallas, TX, Remote Learning

2023

Software Engineer Training - Relevant Technical Skills Covered: Computer Science Concepts Frontend and Backend Frameworks. Data Structures and Algorithms. HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Node.js | Express.js | MongoDB | Mongoose | React

Google UX Design Professional Certificate | Remote Learning

2023

Dallas College, Irving, Texas, completed 60 credits towards AA Diagnostic Medical Sonography

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Registrar - Patient Access, Medical City Las Colinas, Irving, Texas

2020-2021

- Responsible for obtaining complete and accurate demographic and financial information from a variety of sources, such as: patient interviews and in-house departments.
- Processed inpatient and outpatient registration of over 50 patients a day for the emergency department, front desk, ICU, medical-surgical, and labor and delivery.
- Identified and registered patients efficiently using Meditech, an electronic health record software, to ensure correct claims processing and patient privacy guidelines are followed.
- Ensured confidentiality was adhered to when processing financial payments to coincide with correct patient accounts with collections between \$500-\$1,000 per week.

Parent Liaison Volunteer - Jack E. Singley Academy, Irving, Texas

2019-2020

- Assisted in parent meetings, participated in crafting materials for various school activities, and was a teacher's aide.
- Helped parents, most of whom have English as their second language, discuss and analyze chapters as well as explore words they have difficulty understanding to help with their English proficiency and comprehension.

Art Teacher - Falak Arts, Coppell, Texas

2016

- Taught a class to a group of five or more children whose ages ranged from four to eighteen years old.
- Adapted class material to fit a student's development and artistic ability in order to motivate the student to develop their skills.

Victoria's Secret, Grapevine, Texas

2013-2017

- Demonstrated exceptional customer service skills by consistently resolving complaints and fostering positive relationships with customers.
- Oversaw store inventory activities including ordering and requisitions, stocking, and shipment receiving of inventory of up to \$10,000 worth of merchandise.
- Responsible for setting and arranging the visual of the store by managing floor sets and maintaining up to date knowledge
 of all products and services for promotions and marketing.
- Participated in Victoria's Secret AIM (Associates Interested in Management) program which led to opportunities to travel for work to take part in floor sets to open new stores around the DFW area and Oklahoma.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS: Promoted twice in two years from Sales Associate to Visual Tech in under a year and then to Merchandise Flow Supervisor due to my great leadership qualities, strong attention to detail and my ability to work well with others by influencing colleagues in a positive manner.